

# KELVIN LEUNG

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT ME**

A positive and self-motivated full-stack developer with 7+ years of work experience in many different front-end and back-end languages, responsive frameworks, database, mobile app development with Java for Android devices & Swift for iOS devices, and best code practices.

# CONTACT

# Address:

Brisbane, Australia

#### Phone:

+ 61 425 600 216

#### Email:

kelvinleung.aus@gmail.com

#### Website:

http://kelvinleung.me

# LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/kelvinlwy

## **SKILLS**

# **Mobile Development:**Android • iOS

**Programming Languages:**JS • Java • Swift • Object-C • PHP • SQL

#### Web Technologies:

Node.js • CSS3 • HTML5 • Jquery • React.Js • Angular.Js

#### Database:

MySQL • PostgreSQL • MongoDB

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Co-Founder & Tech Lead

# HAPPY DINOSAUR PTY LTD

2017 - Present

Happy Dinosaur is an innovative advertising startup whose strategy is utilising spaces on takeaway coffee cup as medium and cafes as hubs to deliver clients' business message to target audiences in local communities.

My lead role is to design & develop both web & mobile platform for online system through performing requirements analysis, design, technology sourcing to implementation, maintenance, and product analysis; manage digital marketing and social media advertising.

# Full Stack Web App Developer

#### **CHAPTECH**

Mar, 2017 - Sep, 2017

I am responsible for building a web platform written in modern software technologies. My responsibilities:

- Develop a complex web application from scratch for both frontend (with HTML5, CSS3, ReactJS) and backend (with HapiJS, NodeJS, MySQL)
- Implement GIS by using Mapbox API
- API design and development
- Testing, debugging, troubleshooting, maintainence, and application stability & performance improvement

# Android Lead & Web Developer

## **IRECRUIT AUSTRALIA**

May 2016 - Mar, 2017

I am responsible for the full lifecycle Android development through design, project architecture, implementation to debugging & troubleshooting, testing, and product release; the web application front-end development from project planning to translating UI design into code and handling & presenting business logic visually in the web interface.

## **Mobile App Developer**

## **LOCATRIX COMMUNICATIONS**

Jun 2011 - Apr, 2016

- Professional Android development with Java & iOS development with Swift
- Involved in full lifecycle for both enterprise internal & commerical mobile app development from scratch to release

Customer Service Coordinator

**VANTEC WORLD TRANSPORT(HK) LTD** 

Air Export Ops Officer

**UPS SUPPLY CHAIN SOLUTIONS** 

# **EDUCATION**

# **Griffith University**

## **BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING**

2008 - 2011

Bachelor of Engineering, Electronic & Computer Engineering with Class IIA Honours

# **REFERENCE**

# ALEKSANDAR SVETSKI

Former CEO, iRecruit Australia Phone: +61 417 165 003

# **MARK WHITE**

CEO, Locatrix Communications Phone: +61 438 900 880